Okay, most people will
never grow a YouTube
channel, despite putting more
and more effort into
it, because they never
look at their YouTube
pipeline and ask, where's
the block stopping the
water from flowing so
that it can get
to the marketing and
the offer? And what
they do is they
just keep making videos
in the hope that
it will fix itself,
but it won't. And
then 10 weeks later,
they blame the viewers,
they blame YouTube, they
even blame poor old
Ed and his system
saying, but I wrote
the script in the
way he said and
my pipeline didn't fill
up. And after eight
videos, they go back
to posting videos on
TikTok that the good
people of Sierra Leone
can't get enough of
watching. When all they
needed to do was
stop and look at
their pipeline and find
the real reason there
was no progress. And
then once they've discovered
it, learn the lesson
from it and then
take it into the
next video. So basically
all we need to
do to get results
is to learn one
lesson from every video
so we can fix
the bottlenecks. So in
this phase, I'm gonna
train you to become
someone who can see
the reasons their videos
didn't perform. But not
only that, I wanna
train you to get,
so excited by flops
that you're actually happy
when they happen because
you'll look for the
reason, you'll fix it
in the future and
you will actually level
up as a result.
I'm also gonna show
you how to measure
videos after you've launched
them and a way
to measure that will
grow your business too.
And I'm gonna show
you how to use
AI to work out
why a video performed
or why it did
not so you can
get super fast insights.
Now, before we move
on, there is one
thing I have to
ask of members. I've
had people email me
four months into this
going, Ed, I'm doing
everything you said and
I'm not gonna do
it again. I'm not
getting any more views.
So I look at
their channel and I
go, this person is
doing nothing I've told
them to do at
all. They think they
are, but they just
can't see the massive
bottlenecks that I can.
So I usually return
and say, hey, sorry
to hear that. Any
reason you didn't come
to me or any
of my team of
pros in the Discord
after every video you
posted that didn't hit
your expectations and say,
why is this happening?
So we can point
it out to you
and stop you making
the same mistake over
and over again for
10 videos like you've
done. Nobody has ever
replied to that message.
Because I was being
lazy, Ed. We have
13 hours a day
of Discord support right
now. We have four
to five hours of
live calls a week.
That is 95 hours
a week. You can
get feedback and help.
Spotting issues yourself, it's
very hard. Spotting them
when you've got multiple
civil play buttons, 2
million words of written
scripts, hundreds of videos
produced, years of obsessing
over YouTube and having
seen it all means
it's not really that
big a deal for
me. And that's just
me, bolt on all
of my team's experience
and not asking us
to help you to
learn a lesson. So
I'm not asking you
to help me. I'm
asking you to help
me. This is just
dumb. And you paid
for it. So, like,
use it. Okay, so
now move on to
the next video where
I'm going to turn
you from a negative
Nancy to a positive
Pete so that you
don't quit when you
go backwards before you
go forwards with all
your results. And trust
me, you're going to
want to quit. As
you can hopefully know
by now, that's how
this whole system works.